Aung Kaung Myat

Frontend Developer

Aung Kaung Myat

103/30, Tambon Wat Ket Amphoe Mueang Chiang Mai, Chang Wat Chiang Mai, Thailand (+66)937840876

kaungmyat9504@protonmail.com GitHub | LinkedIn | Portfolio | Email | Bento

Summary

Hi there! I'm a software developer with 2 years of experience specializing in React, React Native, NextJS, and NodeJS. I'm always eager to learn new technologies and contribute to challenging projects.

Skills

Front-End: JavaScript, TypeScript, React, React Native, Next.Js, Tailwind CSS, ShadCn

Back-End: NodeJS, ExpressJS, MongoDB,PHP, Laravel, MySQL, Firebase

Tools: Git, GitHub, Redux, Redux Toolkit, React Query, React Navigation, Vercel, Stripe, Cloudinary, OpenAl, Clerk, Other JavaScript Libraries

Experience

ACE Data Systems Ltd. / Mobile Developer

Full - Time

FEBRUARY 2023 - MAY 2024, Yangon, Myanmar

- Built a secure and user-friendly mobile banking app with React Native. Users manage finances, transfer money, mobile top up, qr scan pay and pay bills seamlessly on the go.
- Worked closely with designers to ensure the correct implementation of UI components, layouts, and visuals.
- Delivered high-quality apps on time, implementing complex features, optimizing performance, and collaborating with cross-functional teams to achieve project goals.
- Developed user-friendly mobile screens and features to effectively optimize user experience.
- Built reusable code that is scalable and optimized for performance.
- Created appropriate integration strategies with server-side components and APIs.
- Utilized version control systems and source code management tools (e.g., GIT) to keep track of code.
- Tested, debugged, and optimized mobile applications using various tools and techniques.
- Troubleshoot responsive, flexbox, and functional issues across multiple mobile devices.
- Implemented native features like fingerprint authentication for enhanced security.
- Optimized app performance for scalability, ensuring

smooth handling of high transaction volumes.

Theory IT Solutions / Front-End Developer

Freelance

SEPTEMBER 2023 - Present, Yangon, Myanmar

- Designed and implemented user interfaces for login, sign up, and user profiles.
- Handled form validation and data manipulation to ensure smooth user interaction and data integrity.
- Integrated seamlessly with APIs to retrieve learning materials, track user progress, and store user data securely.
- Implemented responsive UI elements for optimal viewing across various mobile devices.
- Conducted rigorous testing to guarantee a user-friendly and bug-free learning experience.

Education

Zwe Than Private School / High School

JUNE 2018 - JUNE 2020, Ye-U, Sagaing, Myanmar

- Completed coursework with a focus on science majors.
- Graduated with honors, demonstrating strong academic performance.

Fairway Technology / Certification Program

NOVEMBER 2021 - FEBRUARY 2023, Yangon, Myanmar

- Gained expertise in web development standards, including HTML, CSS, and JavaScript.
- Developed responsive and interactive web applications using Bootstrap and PHP/MySQL.
- Mastered the Laravel framework for efficient server-side programming and application logic.

Projects

Meeting / Personal Project

Tech Stacks: Next.Js, TS, Clerk, React Stream, Tailwind Css <u>Demo Link</u>

- Leveraged Next.js for server-side rendering and efficient routing, ensuring a fast and dynamic user experience.
- Utilized React Stream for robust real-time video and audio communication, enabling high-fidelity video meetings.
- Integrated TypeScript for static typing and improved code maintainability.
- Implemented user authentication and authorization protocols to ensure secure meeting access.
- Developed functionalities for managing and storing meeting recordings.

Coffee App / Personal Project

Tech Stacks: React Native, Zustand, React Navigation, TypeScript Source Code

- Browse through different coffee and beans categories
- View detailed information for each coffee and coffee beans, including name, origin, roast level, description, and price.
- Add and remove coffee, and beans from the cart, manage quantities.
- Save favorite coffee, and beans for easy access and Track past orders and reorder favorites.

Volunteer

Lara.Camp Conference

SEPTEMBER 2023, Virtual Meeting

- Volunteered as a panelist at the Lara.camp online conference.
- Engaged with fellow panelists and participants to foster meaningful dialogue and exchange of ideas.
- Demonstrated strong communication skills and subject matter knowledge throughout the conference sessions.
- Collaborated with conference organizers to ensure the smooth execution of panel sessions and overall event success.